I'm Mimian Murakawa, your Candy Tune Pink color representative.
I'm Mian Murakawa and I'm in charge of the pink section of Candy Tune.
I think I'm serious.
I think I'm not pretty enough, or I think she has a good point, or I think she's nice.
When I look at people who are doing a better job, or at amazing people in the world, I wonder why I am the way I am.
When I look at the people who are doing good work, or when I look at the amazing people in the world, I wonder why I am the way I am, even though there are so many people in the world on a large scale.
I always had a negative feeling that I was good at something and I was not good enough.
My first impression of her is that she seems to be a little bit shallow.
I've been told that she doesn't seem to think about anything and that she seems to enjoy life.
That's the way I wanted to be seen.
I like sparkling things, so I like sparkling things like this.
I like sparkling things, so I like sparkling things like this and things that combine beauty and cuteness well.
I love clothes that have a little bit of both, and I think that's what men and women like the most.
I like clothes so much that I sometimes make clothes once every two years or so. I live in Japan.
It's the hardest, toughest, and most exhausting time, but I can feel the light shining from deep within my eyes,
I have realized every time that this is what I want to do,
I feel that I am myself most when I am making clothes or thinking about it.
There are so many people. I have been told that it is difficult to live here, so I wondered how it would be,
I wondered how it would be, but I found that people walk around as if they are not interested in other people. That's why I thought Tokyo was a very comfortable place to live.
There are many people who are not interested in other people, and Harajuku in particular has a lot of foreign residents, so I am doing cross-cultural activities in my own ears.
I am going to be an idol from now on.
I have been doing the same thing for the past seven and a half years, but I really feel that I want to keep smiling.
But I am a crier, so I cry at various times, but I would like to continue to stand on stage with a smile on my face as long as possible.
I cry. I am happy, sad, and in pain. All of them.
I've been doing this for seven and a half years, so I don't think people want me anymore.
I think my fans are wondering when I'm going to quit,
This negativity stems from my deep-rooted negativity,
I thought the world thought so, too,
When I was told that I was not interested in idols,
When I told him that I was, he said that I should definitely do it,
I was really happy to hear that I should definitely try it,
I felt that even someone like me would be sought after.
I still can't believe it. We had been preparing since November and December of last year,
Two more weeks means only ten more days, right?
I still don't feel it yet.
There is so much going on, I don't know.
For those who have known me for the past seven and a half years,
I think the impression is totally different from those who know me for the past seven and a half years, as if I have already had nothing but setbacks.
I had to live and work with the feeling that I was sorry to my fans for not being selected for the group, and I have never been selected,
I have always lived with that in my heart, so it was a big setback for me, and I feel that the past seven and a half years have been a total setback.
I feel that the past seven and a half years have been a total setback for me. I want to teach the members everything I can.
I want to teach the members everything I can,
I want to become a kind and strong woman with a stronger heart,
I want to be a kind and strong woman with a strong heart and save everyone in Candy Tune with my love.
I used to hate myself so much. I was negative,
But my fans loved me so much and kept telling me how much they loved me, so one day I suddenly realized that if I said I hated myself, I would be denying the people who loved me. One day I suddenly realized that if I said I didn't like myself, I would be denying the people who told me they loved me.
I realized that the best way for me to repay my fans is to continue to love myself more and to stay positive no matter what.
The only reason for me to be an idol is to make my fans happy.
I also want to make all the members of CandyChu, the staff at the office, and everyone who is involved with us happy.
That's my reason for being an idol.
It is the reason why I am an idol, and it is one of my unwavering goals.
CandyChu is something I absolutely want to protect.